<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
  <compression>None</compression>
  <version>DarkSouls3</version>
  <bigendian>False</bigendian>
  <entries>
    <text id="40">A Scenic Flatstone yet to be polished.
Purchase to reveal its precious gift.

N.B. Yields items from up to ver. 1.02 of the game.</text>
    <text id="41">%null%</text>
    <text id="42">%null%</text>
    <text id="43">%null%</text>
    <text id="44">%null%</text>
    <text id="45">%null%</text>
    <text id="46">%null%</text>
    <text id="47">%null%</text>
    <text id="48">%null%</text>
    <text id="49">%null%</text>
    <text id="50">A Scenic Flatstone yet to be polished.
Purchase to reveal its precious gift.
This piece was chosen for its remarkable size.

N.B. Yields items from up to ver. 1.02 of the game.</text>
    <text id="70">A Deep Scenic Flatstone yet to be polished.
Purchase to reveal its precious gift.
This piece was chosen for its remarkable size.</text>
    <text id="71">%null%</text>
    <text id="72">%null%</text>
    <text id="73">%null%</text>
    <text id="74">%null%</text>
    <text id="75">%null%</text>
    <text id="76">%null%</text>
    <text id="77">%null%</text>
    <text id="78">%null%</text>
    <text id="79">%null%</text>
    <text id="80">A Deep Scenic Flatstone yet to be polished.
Purchase to reveal its precious gift.

N.B. Yields items from up to ver. 1.02 of the game.</text>
    <text id="81">%null%</text>
    <text id="82">%null%</text>
    <text id="83">%null%</text>
    <text id="84">%null%</text>
    <text id="85">%null%</text>
    <text id="86">%null%</text>
    <text id="87">%null%</text>
    <text id="88">%null%</text>
    <text id="89">%null%</text>
    <text id="90">A Deep Scenic Flatstone yet to be polished.
Purchase to reveal its precious gift.
This piece was chosen for its remarkable size.

N.B. Yields items from up to ver. 1.02 of the game.</text>
    <text id="1600">%null%</text>
    <text id="1601">%null%</text>
    <text id="1602">%null%</text>
    <text id="1603">%null%</text>
    <text id="1604">%null%</text>
    <text id="1605">%null%</text>
    <text id="1606">%null%</text>
    <text id="1607">%null%</text>
    <text id="1608">%null%</text>
    <text id="1609">%null%</text>
    <text id="1610">%null%</text>
    <text id="2070">The will of the Harmonia, left upon their defeat.

The power of its namesake can be unlocked by performing a relic rite.

A tiny farming village was besieged by bandits, who proceeded to ravage both its plots and people.

A young village girl, seeking help, dashed into the forest, where she prayed to the statue of a protective deity that held a weapon raised overhead.

By the end the village was steeped in red and settled in silence. The village girl, drenched in blood, stood with a vacant stare and a heroic weapon in her grip.</text>
    <text id="2071">An inhuman will, left in the wake of battle.

The power of its namesake can be unlocked by performing a relic rite.

A tiny farming village was besieged by bandits, who proceeded to ravage both its plots and people.

A young village girl, seeking help, dashed into the forest, where she prayed to the statue of a protective deity that held a weapon raised overhead.

By the end the village was steeped in red and settled in silence. The village girl, drenched in blood, stood with a vacant stare and a heroic weapon in her grip.</text>
    <text id="2072">%null%</text>
    <text id="2073">%null%</text>
    <text id="2074">%null%</text>
    <text id="2075">%null%</text>
    <text id="2076">%null%</text>
    <text id="2077">%null%</text>
    <text id="2078">%null%</text>
    <text id="2079">%null%</text>
    <text id="2080">The night belonging to Straghess, left upon its defeat.

The power of its namesake can be unlocked by performing a relic rite.

The traces left behind by countless battles were pelted by rains, transported by muddy streams, and collected in deposits.

This mixture of remorse, desperation, and sorrow eventually formed legs, stood of its own accord, and finally, voiced a curse that would be its mantra.

"Smash, smash, smash the Night..."</text>
    <text id="19000">Fast-acting medicine for a disease that afflicted the Albinaurics that works by removing invasive contaminants.

The vassal who developed the medicine did so by testing it on his own body. It was successful, and used to treat patients, but the vassal himself passed, his sickness already too advanced.

Both the disease and the cure are not mentioned in the annals of history, and the person responsible for their omission is unknown.
</text>
    <text id="19001">A note left by the Scholar addressed to those in pursuit of the truth, summarizing the events that transpired in Limveld.

"Analysis can be painful, but the benefit outweighs the sacrifice.

To whomever succeeds me in my work: May your endless journeys lead to enlightenment."</text>
    <text id="19050">A well-worn leather case for storing a monocle. The scuffs and crease marks are proof of its owner's adoration.

The Scholar left evidence of his own death to the Undertaker. It was the always-candid Scholar's form of a farewell.

"Now...what do I do?"</text>
    <text id="19051">その約束が彼女に目的を与え、ネックレスを握りしめることを可能にした。</text>
  </entries>
</fmg>