<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="101000">The Wylder departed from his faraway home, braving the sea of fog to reach Limveld.

A Nightfarer's forays wither the soul and cloud recollection, causing one night to bleed into the next. But of one thing he remained certain.

That he must track down the Nightlord, and bury it. There was no choice.

He repeated the words to himself, all the while clenching a precious object in his hand. A solitary earring, its counterpart long lost.</text>
<text id="101001">%null%</text>
<text id="101002">%null%</text>
<text id="101003">%null%</text>
<text id="101004">%null%</text>
<text id="101005">%null%</text>
<text id="101006">%null%</text>
<text id="101007">%null%</text>
<text id="101008">%null%</text>
<text id="101009">%null%</text>
<text id="101010">In a corner of the Roundtable Hold, light shines in through the ceiling to a dimly-lit room.

There stood the Wylder, holding the solitary earring up to the light, casting a pattern on the wall that he could not comprehend.

The Wylder was sure that it was some word, or perhaps a phrase, but he could not recall it.

Where had he misplaced the earring? If he only had the its counterpart, surely the meaning could be divined.</text>
<text id="101011">%null%</text>
<text id="101012">%null%</text>
<text id="101013">%null%</text>
<text id="101014">%null%</text>
<text id="101015">%null%</text>
<text id="101016">%null%</text>
<text id="101017">%null%</text>
<text id="101018">%null%</text>
<text id="101019">%null%</text>
<text id="101020">He dreamt of his home.

Two horses galloping across Windwail Knoll. They were a healthy pair of twins, which was rare. To the Wylder,
and to         , the horses were special.

Upon a hill they ran abreast. He looked at her, hair dancing in the wind, and saw the earring on her left ear. But he could not recall a face.

"My lord Wylder, how are you today?"

The voice of the Iron Menial awakened him. Time for another errand, no doubt.</text>
<text id="101021">%null%</text>
<text id="101022">%null%</text>
<text id="101023">%null%</text>
<text id="101024">%null%</text>
<text id="101025">%null%</text>
<text id="101026">%null%</text>
<text id="101027">%null%</text>
<text id="101028">%null%</text>
<text id="101029">%null%</text>
<text id="101030">Clutching the now solitary earring, the Wylder drifted off into sleep.

The sun was setting on Windwail Knoll, and as if in deference to its name, a gale howled.

The dreaded winter was approaching. By the time of the first frost, he knew that his sister would be far along her journey. The Wylder fell silent, and         , flashing her signature smile, flicked her earring with her finger.

"Good bye for now, dear brother. Once we're done, we'll meet again."

He could not remember her name, but he always remembered these parting words.</text>
<text id="101031">%null%</text>
<text id="101032">%null%</text>
<text id="101033">%null%</text>
<text id="101034">%null%</text>
<text id="101035">%null%</text>
<text id="101036">%null%</text>
<text id="101037">%null%</text>
<text id="101038">%null%</text>
<text id="101039">%null%</text>
<text id="101040">The Wylder continued to fight, never mentioning his younger sister. There was no way forward except to soldier through the war at hand.

He returned to the Roundtable Hold that day to discover a note from the Iron Menial.

"I've considered what might explain your singular obsession with that earring.

Then it came to me.
The two of you...possess a striking likeness.
So much so that I simply cannot deny it.

There is something that you must know.
Please check the study."</text>
<text id="101041">%null%</text>
<text id="101042">%null%</text>
<text id="101043">%null%</text>
<text id="101044">%null%</text>
<text id="101045">%null%</text>
<text id="101046">%null%</text>
<text id="101047">%null%</text>
<text id="101048">%null%</text>
<text id="101049">%null%</text>
<text id="101050">The Wylder had the same dream time and time again.

A long night persists, driving his clansfolk to madness. After a horrific battle, all that remains upon Windwail Knoll is a sea of gravestones. After the deaths of cousin Farhad, Little Shirin, and his own father, the clan's chieftain, the Wylder discovers that only he remains.

And now, only he can avenge his clan. Only he can bring an end to the Night.
But even if he can...

"Once we're done, it will be goodbye."

Even if the Night were extinguished, the twin horses will never gallop aside one another again.</text>
<text id="101051">%null%</text>
<text id="101052">%null%</text>
<text id="101053">%null%</text>
<text id="101054">%null%</text>
<text id="101055">%null%</text>
<text id="101056">%null%</text>
<text id="101057">%null%</text>
<text id="101058">%null%</text>
<text id="101059">%null%</text>
<text id="101060">Holding his greatsword, the Wylder drifted off to sleep.

Out of nowhere, he heard the rustle of cloth, then the clink of something being placed on the table.

The Wylder awoke, and slowly sat up.</text>
<text id="101061">%null%</text>
<text id="101062">%null%</text>
<text id="101063">%null%</text>
<text id="101064">%null%</text>
<text id="101065">%null%</text>
<text id="101066">%null%</text>
<text id="101067">%null%</text>
<text id="101068">%null%</text>
<text id="101069">%null%</text>
<text id="101070">The Silver Tear he grasped gently throbbed. The Wylder discovered a familiar brooch by his belongings.

In his tribe, when one warrior gave such a gift to another, it was a promise to ever fight side-by-side, whether separated by land or sea. Did his young sister remember such customs?

He pinned the brooch to his coat, as was their practice, and gently placed his hand upon it.

"Once we're done, it'll be goodbye."

He knew the twin horses would never run free again, as once they did, side by side. But perhaps just one could gallop onward.</text>
<text id="101071">%null%</text>
<text id="101072">%null%</text>
<text id="101073">%null%</text>
<text id="101074">%null%</text>
<text id="101075">%null%</text>
<text id="101076">%null%</text>
<text id="101077">%null%</text>
<text id="101078">%null%</text>
<text id="101079">%null%</text>
<text id="101080">After a time, a new Nightlord came to be.

The Roundtable Hold, spared from annihilation, would be formed anew. In preparation for a new Night.

But would it be enough to free the Priestess? He would never know.

The Nightlord lumbered on. Indifferent to whether or not the twin horses would ever ride again.</text>
<text id="102000">A letter from the Iron Menial, written shortly after the Duchess was summoned to the Roundtable Hold.

"We have awaited your arrival with great anticipation. As Priestess you shall guide the Roundtable Hold to victory over the Nightlord. I was chosen to assist you in whatever way I can.

The garden is graced with beautiful flowers, and the study filled with rare books, new and old, by all manner of authors and on every subject fathomable. If I may I ask, what are your preferences for meals? I will serve whatever you wish.

One last thing. Perhaps you'd be amicable to a change of attire. You are a righteous thief no longer. Now you are the honorable Priestess of the Hold."</text>
<text id="102001">%null%</text>
<text id="102002">%null%</text>
<text id="102003">%null%</text>
<text id="102004">%null%</text>
<text id="102005">%null%</text>
<text id="102006">%null%</text>
<text id="102007">%null%</text>
<text id="102008">%null%</text>
<text id="102009">%null%</text>
<text id="102010">A letter from the Iron Menial, written after the Wylder
was summoned to the Roundtable Hold.

"I trust that our newly-welcomed champion has had a moment to gain his bearings.

He appears to have sustained injuries in the outside world, before he was drawn here. Rest assured, I will make certain that he is properly cared for.

In any case, I am delighted to welcome a new Nightfarer to our family. He seems to be the master of a very large sword. No doubt, he will make good use of it in our campaign against the Night."</text>
<text id="102011">%null%</text>
<text id="102012">%null%</text>
<text id="102013">%null%</text>
<text id="102014">%null%</text>
<text id="102015">%null%</text>
<text id="102016">%null%</text>
<text id="102017">%null%</text>
<text id="102018">%null%</text>
<text id="102019">%null%</text>
<text id="102020">A routine letter from the Iron Menial concerning everyday affairs.

"Baking the bread you requested is proving to be far more difficult than expected.

I've recruited the Raider to assess the results of my trials, and surely this will help me approach your specifications.

Which reminds me, the Raider said he wishes to speak to you about something. Perhaps you might pay him a visit?"</text>
<text id="102021">%null%</text>
<text id="102022">%null%</text>
<text id="102023">%null%</text>
<text id="102024">%null%</text>
<text id="102025">%null%</text>
<text id="102026">%null%</text>
<text id="102027">%null%</text>
<text id="102028">%null%</text>
<text id="102029">%null%</text>
<text id="102030">A letter from the Iron Menial that appears to have been rewritten several times.

"I know you are worried for the Wylder. But such things happen more than you might imagine.

It appears that the injuries he sustained in the outside world, before his arrival here, have made him terribly weak.

If we should defeat the Nightlord, as we yearn to do, I am afraid the Wylder may not return alive.

And yet we must carry on, as tragic as it is."</text>
<text id="102031">%null%</text>
<text id="102032">%null%</text>
<text id="102033">%null%</text>
<text id="102034">%null%</text>
<text id="102035">%null%</text>
<text id="102036">%null%</text>
<text id="102037">%null%</text>
<text id="102038">%null%</text>
<text id="102039">%null%</text>
<text id="102040">A letter from the Iron Menial that appears to have been rewritten several times.

"I know you are worried for the Wylder. But such things happen more than you might imagine.

It appears that the injuries he sustained in the outside world, before his arrival here, have made him terribly weak.

If we should defeat the Nightlord, as we yearn to do, I am afraid the Wylder may not return alive.

And yet we must carry on, as tragic as it is."</text>
<text id="102041">%null%</text>
<text id="102042">%null%</text>
<text id="102043">%null%</text>
<text id="102044">%null%</text>
<text id="102045">%null%</text>
<text id="102046">%null%</text>
<text id="102047">%null%</text>
<text id="102048">%null%</text>
<text id="102049">%null%</text>
<text id="102050">A letter from the Iron Menial written in an anxious, scrawled script.

"My lady Priestess, I am well aware of your grave concern for the Wylder.

You should know that when I checked in on him, he appeared to be making preparations of a sort.

And today he is nowhere to be seen.

The Wylder's weakened constitution places him at risk. Please seek him out. He should be somewhere inside the Roundtable Hold."</text>
<text id="102051">%null%</text>
<text id="102052">%null%</text>
<text id="102053">%null%</text>
<text id="102054">%null%</text>
<text id="102055">%null%</text>
<text id="102056">%null%</text>
<text id="102057">%null%</text>
<text id="102058">%null%</text>
<text id="102059">%null%</text>
<text id="102060">A letter from the Iron Menial, written with even greater care than usual.

"Those who fare against the Night find that even their most cherished memories eventually dissipate. It is nothing less than a miracle that you've restored your memories of your brother. I understand how concerned you must be for what lies ahead.

But there is one thing we must never forget. We were beckoned here for one reason and one reason only. To bring an end to the Nightlord.

Many among us are gravely concerned for you, my lady Priestess, the Raider especially so. Perhaps you should lend him your ear."</text>
<text id="102061">%null%</text>
<text id="102062">%null%</text>
<text id="102063">%null%</text>
<text id="102064">%null%</text>
<text id="102065">%null%</text>
<text id="102066">%null%</text>
<text id="102067">%null%</text>
<text id="102068">%null%</text>
<text id="102069">%null%</text>
<text id="102070">A letter from the Iron Menial, that was torn up and discarded without ever reaching its addressee.

"As you are well aware, my lady Priestess, you are bound to the Roundtable Hold.

But if the object were not born of flesh and blood, it could venture beyond the Roundtable Hold. But to make such a thing possible..."

The Duchess clutched the paper scraps in her hand, as if clinging to a fleeting dream.</text>
<text id="102071">%null%</text>
<text id="102072">%null%</text>
<text id="102073">%null%</text>
<text id="102074">%null%</text>
<text id="102075">%null%</text>
<text id="102076">%null%</text>
<text id="102077">%null%</text>
<text id="102078">%null%</text>
<text id="102079">%null%</text>
<text id="102080">A letter from the Iron Menial that was torn to pieces then later patched together.

"...But to make such a thing possible, to connect to the Wylder in the outside world, before he draws any closer to death, we require a fetish.

Such a bond could be established if the object that he kept on his person was to receive a blessing.

But the chances of success are slim indeed, and I cannot bear to think of leaving you, lady Priestess, all alone..."</text>
<text id="102081">%null%</text>
<text id="102082">%null%</text>
<text id="102083">%null%</text>
<text id="102084">%null%</text>
<text id="102085">%null%</text>
<text id="102086">%null%</text>
<text id="102087">%null%</text>
<text id="102088">%null%</text>
<text id="102089">%null%</text>
<text id="102090">A letter addressed to the Iron Menial.

"To a dear friend, who has always been true.

Please follow the blessed bond and safeguard my brother's life.

To this end, we must first lay the Nightlord to rest. We need not sacrifice one goal for the other. We can achieve both.

My resolve no longer wavers. Not while I am graced with this barrette."</text>
<text id="103000">The pirates of the coastal waters love nothing more than a worthy rival.

And thus the Raider made his way to Limveld. The encroaching Nightlord was precisely the challenge he wished for. Or so his intuition told him.

The moment he stepped foot in the Roundtable Hold, he knew that he was right. And when he donned the white-horned helmet, he was certain that he could hear it...

...the gentle murmuring of waves of the coastal waters, that were once so familiar.</text>
<text id="103001">%null%</text>
<text id="103002">%null%</text>
<text id="103003">%null%</text>
<text id="103004">%null%</text>
<text id="103005">%null%</text>
<text id="103006">%null%</text>
<text id="103007">%null%</text>
<text id="103008">%null%</text>
<text id="103009">%null%</text>
<text id="103010">The Raider removed the helmet and placed it on the floor with a thunk.

The war with the Night was constant, never leaving an idle moment. And yet, he felt oddly unfulfilled.

"Do you feel the same, old friend?"

As he murmured to himself, he patted the white horns of his beloved helmet. They were chiseled and worn, reminders of the countless battles waged heretofore.

There must be someone who'd pour his soul into a battle to the death. A rival fierce enough to make one's blood boil. He was certain that such a warrior could not be far, and perhaps was even quite close. Maybe right here, in the Roundtable Hold...</text>
<text id="103011">%null%</text>
<text id="103012">%null%</text>
<text id="103013">%null%</text>
<text id="103014">%null%</text>
<text id="103015">%null%</text>
<text id="103016">%null%</text>
<text id="103017">%null%</text>
<text id="103018">%null%</text>
<text id="103019">%null%</text>
<text id="103020">The Tourney of the Lands Between was finished, and once again he found himself peering at his white-horned helmet. It was a good feeling. But he wanted more.

He recalled the words of the Iron Menial.

"The potential to discover a truly worthy opponent."

For the pirates of the coastal waters, such a rival is more precious than any treasure.</text>
<text id="103021">%null%</text>
<text id="103022">%null%</text>
<text id="103023">%null%</text>
<text id="103024">%null%</text>
<text id="103025">%null%</text>
<text id="103026">%null%</text>
<text id="103027">%null%</text>
<text id="103028">%null%</text>
<text id="103029">%null%</text>
<text id="103030">Anticipation of battle reminded him of an old memory from his time sailing the coastal waters.

A wave knocked the Raider onto the shore, and his first mate Weathervane called out to him.

"Ah... Are you alive, Cap'n?"

The Raider replied by slamming a fist into his low-worn helmet, causing a gush of blood. But he paid it no mind.

"Never should have asked."
Weathervane sighed but at the same time appeared to be scribbling some notes. The Raider took notice, and Weathervane brazenly chuckled.

"I've got front row seats to a duel to the death between two bloody beasts. Figured I could make a fortune if I got the details down."</text>
<text id="103031">%null%</text>
<text id="103032">%null%</text>
<text id="103033">%null%</text>
<text id="103034">%null%</text>
<text id="103035">%null%</text>
<text id="103036">%null%</text>
<text id="103037">%null%</text>
<text id="103038">%null%</text>
<text id="103039">%null%</text>
<text id="103040">After the Raider finished the Tourney of the Lands Between, the Ironeye asked him a question.

"White Horn and Black Claw, was it? Intriguing story. But I heard they never settled who'd rule the coastal waters. Why not?"

The assassin of the fellowship had suddenly become quite talkative about naval campaigns.

"Hahah, perhaps we'll never know.
But I can say one thing."

With a smile, the Raider slapped his helmet.

"Pirates of the coastal waters never forget a vow to lock horns. We'd rather die than live as cowards!"</text>
<text id="103041">%null%</text>
<text id="103042">%null%</text>
<text id="103043">%null%</text>
<text id="103044">%null%</text>
<text id="103045">%null%</text>
<text id="103046">%null%</text>
<text id="103047">%null%</text>
<text id="103048">%null%</text>
<text id="103049">%null%</text>
<text id="103050">The Raider waited. For the commencement of the final match of the Tourney of the Lands Between.

But the Iron Menial noticed something amiss with the monument.

"There is no sign of a coming battle.
Perhaps something's happened to your challenger?"

But the Raider was patient.

He knew that this was a time to be patient. And moreover, that his opponent was fond of arriving late.</text>
<text id="103051">%null%</text>
<text id="103052">%null%</text>
<text id="103053">%null%</text>
<text id="103054">%null%</text>
<text id="103055">%null%</text>
<text id="103056">%null%</text>
<text id="103057">%null%</text>
<text id="103058">%null%</text>
<text id="103059">%null%</text>
<text id="103060">The sea breeze reminded him of his memories of the coastal waters.

The Raider sat on the shore where they were arranged to meet. Weathervane pleaded with him.

"Give this one up, Cap'n. He's part of the Night, now."

The Raider peered west, at a sea engulfed by darkness, and punched the white-horned helmet.

"I'll hold on to this for now."

After reminiscing for a moment, he was interrupted by a gentle murmuring of waves. The Raider opened his eyes and gazed silently out at the waters.

He knew where he must go. For when the sea summons them to fight, the call must be answered.</text>
<text id="103061">%null%</text>
<text id="103062">%null%</text>
<text id="103063">%null%</text>
<text id="103064">%null%</text>
<text id="103065">%null%</text>
<text id="103066">%null%</text>
<text id="103067">%null%</text>
<text id="103068">%null%</text>
<text id="103069">%null%</text>
<text id="103070">The final match was held, bringing the Tourney of the Lands Between to its conclusion.

The Raider gave the White Horn helmet back to its owner, and was Black Claw once again. A gentle wind brushed his cheek. He wondered how Weathervane may have recorded their battle in words.

The pirates of the coastal waters love nothing more than a worthy rival.

But these days, the Raider no longer hears the gentle murmur of the waves. For him, the sea churns no longer.</text>
<text id="104000">Mine flesh, partially plated.

Mine hand, with brush.
A window into oneself.

Brushstrokes outline
these fragments of memory.</text>
<text id="104001">%null%</text>
<text id="104002">%null%</text>
<text id="104003">%null%</text>
<text id="104004">%null%</text>
<text id="104005">%null%</text>
<text id="104006">%null%</text>
<text id="104007">%null%</text>
<text id="104008">%null%</text>
<text id="104009">%null%</text>
<text id="104010">The Erdtree

I am an artist.

From the distant Land of Reeds,
washed up on the shore,
inspired by what I saw.

But the piece is incomplete.
Something is missing.</text>
<text id="104011">%null%</text>
<text id="104012">%null%</text>
<text id="104013">%null%</text>
<text id="104014">%null%</text>
<text id="104015">%null%</text>
<text id="104016">%null%</text>
<text id="104017">%null%</text>
<text id="104018">%null%</text>
<text id="104019">%null%</text>
<text id="104020">Flowers

An embracing warmth
from the flowers, the same flowers
that grew in my painter's shed.

I am an artist, painting the Erdtree.
I am a guest, bearing a sword.
I am silent, I am a witness.</text>
<text id="104021">%null%</text>
<text id="104022">%null%</text>
<text id="104023">%null%</text>
<text id="104024">%null%</text>
<text id="104025">%null%</text>
<text id="104026">%null%</text>
<text id="104027">%null%</text>
<text id="104028">%null%</text>
<text id="104029">%null%</text>
<text id="104030">The Guest

I am a guest.
Or perhaps, an executioner.

The guest speaks.

"I will wait
until your Erdtree is complete."</text>
<text id="104031">%null%</text>
<text id="104032">%null%</text>
<text id="104033">%null%</text>
<text id="104034">%null%</text>
<text id="104035">%null%</text>
<text id="104036">%null%</text>
<text id="104037">%null%</text>
<text id="104038">%null%</text>
<text id="104039">%null%</text>
<text id="104040">Old Friend

"The Erdtree" was still incomplete,
and so I drew a sketch, in solace.

Of an old friend from the Land of Reeds,
who speaks not a word.

I will entrust it to my guest.

I cannot complete "The Erdtree"
before another executioner
arrives in the first one's stead.</text>
<text id="104041">%null%</text>
<text id="104042">%null%</text>
<text id="104043">%null%</text>
<text id="104044">%null%</text>
<text id="104045">%null%</text>
<text id="104046">%null%</text>
<text id="104047">%null%</text>
<text id="104048">%null%</text>
<text id="104049">%null%</text>
<text id="104050">The Crucible Knight

A portrait of my guest,
or perhaps, my executioner.

A crucible holds a composite.
My guest could not bear
to render a judgment.

Here at the painter's shed,
overlooking the Erdtree.
Until the very end.</text>
<text id="104051">%null%</text>
<text id="104052">%null%</text>
<text id="104053">%null%</text>
<text id="104054">%null%</text>
<text id="104055">%null%</text>
<text id="104056">%null%</text>
<text id="104057">%null%</text>
<text id="104058">%null%</text>
<text id="104059">%null%</text>
<text id="104060">The Executor

Two faces, one sword.
Such is my nature.

A soul drenched in blood.
Yet willing to face the Night.

And perhaps
when the Night has passed.
I will complete "The Erdtree."</text>
<text id="105000">Though my fellows call me by the name of "Recluse," mine origin is as one of many—a witch of the deep woods.

From mine seclusion amongst the trees, cause did I have to journey forth, to Limveld.

For I had mind to search—for a certain something, coiled in shadow.</text>
<text id="105001">%null%</text>
<text id="105002">%null%</text>
<text id="105003">%null%</text>
<text id="105004">%null%</text>
<text id="105005">%null%</text>
<text id="105006">%null%</text>
<text id="105007">%null%</text>
<text id="105008">%null%</text>
<text id="105009">%null%</text>
<text id="105010">I search for, yes, my "beloved infant."

If I am to find it, I must recognize the signs that shall point the way. First, I aim to approach the menial.

The Beloved Infant:
The being that I, as a witch, birthed.
It was never a true name bequeathed, though with a certain mirth we spoke of it as "the gnawling."

Following a trail of ancient magic, its whereabouts are approximately known—it remaineth in somewhere in Limveld, I am sure.

I seek a Shard of Night, that the babe's connection to the night might be ascertained.</text>
<text id="105011">%null%</text>
<text id="105012">%null%</text>
<text id="105013">%null%</text>
<text id="105014">%null%</text>
<text id="105015">%null%</text>
<text id="105016">%null%</text>
<text id="105017">%null%</text>
<text id="105018">%null%</text>
<text id="105019">%null%</text>
<text id="105020">While I await the outcome of the menial's investigation, my thoughts turn to an old companion, now passed. For my search, in some ways, is an atonement for what happened to her.

The Witch of the Wheel:
An old friend, who is learned in the same ways as I. She was, in a sense, the Infant's nurse.

The gnawling would eat anything and everything, in quantities most vast. As such, I left its feeding to mine old companion.

The witch of the wheel was a woman of deceit. Her wiles were sword and shield to her.</text>
<text id="105021">The vestiges procured were proof enough her theory held water. The proliferation of lords was just a precursor, and that behind their creation was an existence which guided them to the power required to ascend.

She only needed to gather a little more, and all would become clear.</text>
<text id="105022">She'd had the right idea all along—the power of Night displayed qualities all too similar to an ancient magic. It felt intimate, nostalgic, even personal to her...

The girl was close by, she was certain.</text>
<text id="105023">%null%</text>
<text id="105024">%null%</text>
<text id="105025">%null%</text>
<text id="105026">%null%</text>
<text id="105027">%null%</text>
<text id="105028">%null%</text>
<text id="105029">%null%</text>
<text id="105030">The menial left a note.

His investigation seemeth to have borne fruit. From the Night Shard, vestiges of the Infant can be traced. I shall ask for the shard's return, that I might verify this myself.

The Menial:
Appears to be a carved mannequin-like creature.
Hath taken to aiding me in my search.

Perhaps I have tasked him overmuch, I have seen him converse passing little with the other warriors of late. His presence seemeth to recede at the Roundtable.</text>
<text id="105031">%null%</text>
<text id="105032">%null%</text>
<text id="105033">%null%</text>
<text id="105034">%null%</text>
<text id="105035">%null%</text>
<text id="105036">%null%</text>
<text id="105037">%null%</text>
<text id="105038">%null%</text>
<text id="105039">%null%</text>
<text id="105040">Using the Night Shard, I found a vestige connected to the Infant. Here is all I have learned thus far.

The Vestige of Night:
Teeth marks found in the Night Shard, alongside the Vestige of Night found embedded in the Roundtable Hold. Both seem to radiate an ancient magic which I myself imbued.

I am certain, after mine Infant disappeared itself that day, it must have had an audience with the Nightlord.

It ravened as if its appetite knew no bound—it would devour shadows of any stripe. The Nightlord's own shade surely seemed irresistible to it. What must have become of my creature, after it did feast...</text>
<text id="105041">%null%</text>
<text id="105042">%null%</text>
<text id="105043">%null%</text>
<text id="105044">%null%</text>
<text id="105045">%null%</text>
<text id="105046">%null%</text>
<text id="105047">%null%</text>
<text id="105048">%null%</text>
<text id="105049">%null%</text>
<text id="105050">I sensed another familiar magic within the Vestige of Night. I believe now that mine old companion is the key to finding the Infant. The Witch of the Wheel, who should be long departed.

Using the clues I have gathered, I must seek her in her hiding place within the Roundtable Hold.

The Demise of the Witch of the Wheel:
During a great clash of armies, the Infant overran the enemy, devouring their shadows. It was then that it lost itself, and bared its fangs at us.
With time I have come to understand. It was yet young, and afraid, and I did not think to take it in my arms. To offer comfort of any kind.
The price I paid was the loss of an old friend. I still remember, clear as day, her remains—shorn of any shadow.</text>
<text id="105051">%null%</text>
<text id="105052">%null%</text>
<text id="105053">%null%</text>
<text id="105054">%null%</text>
<text id="105055">%null%</text>
<text id="105056">%null%</text>
<text id="105057">%null%</text>
<text id="105058">%null%</text>
<text id="105059">%null%</text>
<text id="105060">The crying of a babe rang out in the place where it all began. Reaching the voice which seemed to guide her steps, the Recluse gently cradled the babe in her arms.

The Witch of the Wheel expressed her thanks, and then faded away. Taking up the robe left behind, the Recluse made her exit.</text>
<text id="105061">%null%</text>
<text id="105062">%null%</text>
<text id="105063">%null%</text>
<text id="105064">%null%</text>
<text id="105065">%null%</text>
<text id="105066">%null%</text>
<text id="105067">%null%</text>
<text id="105068">%null%</text>
<text id="105069">%null%</text>
<text id="105070">The child with the Nightlord bequeathed me the last thing I needed in my search.

Bone-Like Stone:
The Infant's voice can be heard when softly touching the stone.

Please, have patience. I shall come to thee, I swear.</text>
<text id="105071">%null%</text>
<text id="105072">%null%</text>
<text id="105073">%null%</text>
<text id="105074">%null%</text>
<text id="105075">%null%</text>
<text id="105076">%null%</text>
<text id="105077">%null%</text>
<text id="105078">%null%</text>
<text id="105079">%null%</text>
<text id="105080">"I thank thee, for bestowing thy love upon our Night."

Thus did mine old companion speak to me in parting. The words resounded within, as I took the Infant in mine arms.

As I did what I once could not, all those years ago.

The crying hath now ceased. The gentle night within its breast knoweth now a peaceful slumber.</text>
<text id="106000">Instructions sent from the Fellowship to the Ironeye:

Ironeye, beloved child of the Fellowship,

We have received word from Batear that you have fulfilled your duty. Your compensation is on its way.

Remain at your present location—a new, substantial task will soon be upon you, which will likely require journeying to the Lands Between. Details to follow.

Ever your custodian,

Isolde

P.S. Please forget what I said the other day, it was pure balderdash, spoken in frustration.</text>
<text id="106001">%null%</text>
<text id="106002">%null%</text>
<text id="106003">%null%</text>
<text id="106004">%null%</text>
<text id="106005">%null%</text>
<text id="106006">%null%</text>
<text id="106007">%null%</text>
<text id="106008">%null%</text>
<text id="106009">%null%</text>
<text id="106010">Instructions sent from the Fellowship to the Ironeye:

Ironeye, beloved child of the Fellowship,

I am certain you are aware of the destruction of the boarding house in the Dusken Valley.

Root out the traitor and retire him. You can pick up his trail in the Lands Between.

Standard protocol applies—the Fellowship will not involve itself. Travelling expenses, intelligence and allies must all be procured as you work.

Ever your custodian,

Isolde</text>
<text id="106011">%null%</text>
<text id="106012">%null%</text>
<text id="106013">%null%</text>
<text id="106014">%null%</text>
<text id="106015">%null%</text>
<text id="106016">%null%</text>
<text id="106017">%null%</text>
<text id="106018">%null%</text>
<text id="106019">%null%</text>
<text id="106020">A report written by the Ironeye, addressed to the Fellowship:

Isolde, my custodian,

I have no means to deliver this report, but I here shall I record my progress:

Following the traitor's trail has lead me to the Roundtable Hold.

I have made an ally who goes by the name of "Priestess." There have been scant clues to find, but such is the way in this field of work. The work itself proceeds as usual.

Ironeye</text>
<text id="106021">%null%</text>
<text id="106022">%null%</text>
<text id="106023">%null%</text>
<text id="106024">%null%</text>
<text id="106025">%null%</text>
<text id="106026">%null%</text>
<text id="106027">%null%</text>
<text id="106028">%null%</text>
<text id="106029">%null%</text>
<text id="106030">Instructions sent from the Fellowship to the Ironeye:

Ironeye, beloved child of the Fellowship,

I believe you are familiar with "The Monster."

It is clear now that his guardian had been slain long ago. It seems to have happened when the boarding house was destroyed in the Dusken Valley. There is a strong likelihood that the traitor to the Fellowship is indeed the "Monster."

Take every precaution. He was raised by the Fellowship to be the centipedal scion he is, after all.

Ever your custodian,

Isolde</text>
<text id="106031">%null%</text>
<text id="106032">%null%</text>
<text id="106033">%null%</text>
<text id="106034">%null%</text>
<text id="106035">%null%</text>
<text id="106036">%null%</text>
<text id="106037">%null%</text>
<text id="106038">%null%</text>
<text id="106039">%null%</text>
<text id="106040">A report written by the Ironeye, addressed to the Fellowship:

Isolde, my custodian,

I have picked up the trail of the traitor—the Monster. He is a brother of the Fellowship. The battle is sure to be drawn-out, but I shall prevail. I will send a report once the deed is done.

Ironeye

P.S. I found a sealed missive amongst my effects. In accordance with protocol, I shall open it, unless advised otherwise, Master.</text>
<text id="106041">%null%</text>
<text id="106042">%null%</text>
<text id="106043">%null%</text>
<text id="106044">%null%</text>
<text id="106045">%null%</text>
<text id="106046">%null%</text>
<text id="106047">%null%</text>
<text id="106048">%null%</text>
<text id="106049">%null%</text>
<text id="106050">A bloodstained letter, addressed to the Ironeye:

The scions of the Fellowship are fated to be disposed of once they play their part. Thus I had a dream—to wrest the power of the Night and bend the rules which govern our realm.

The scions raised would wander through an endless Night, fighting on and on. A Night that would never break, for their sake, I desired.

But it is a dream most foolish. I should never have mentioned it to you. Free yourself of your misgivings, and walk the path in which you believe.

Ever your custodian,

Isolde</text>
<text id="106051">%null%</text>
<text id="106052">%null%</text>
<text id="106053">%null%</text>
<text id="106054">%null%</text>
<text id="106055">%null%</text>
<text id="106056">%null%</text>
<text id="106057">%null%</text>
<text id="106058">%null%</text>
<text id="106059">%null%</text>
<text id="106060">A report written by the Ironeye, addressed to the Fellowship:

Isolde, my custodian,

I have no means to deliver this report, but I here shall I record my progress:

The traitor has been dealt with. All that remains is to face the Nightlord.

Ironeye

P.S. Fear not, Master—my mind is clear.</text>
<text id="106061">%null%</text>
<text id="106062">%null%</text>
<text id="106063">%null%</text>
<text id="106064">%null%</text>
<text id="106065">%null%</text>
<text id="106066">%null%</text>
<text id="106067">%null%</text>
<text id="106068">%null%</text>
<text id="106069">%null%</text>
<text id="106070">A report written by the Ironeye, addressed to the Fellowship:

Isolde, my custodian,

You were the finest guardian one could hope for.

I desired freedom from the yoke of the Fellowship only because you showed me it was possible.

I have only gratitude for you, Master. For now, my Night shall never end.</text>
<text id="107000">The Guardian was born in the Winged Realm, becoming a knight of the Pinionfolk, sworn to protect its lands and peoples.

In the splintered memories of the Guardian are two "flocks."

The old flock from his home nation, who he failed to protect—who died. And the new flock, who fare with him against the Night.</text>
<text id="107001">%null%</text>
<text id="107002">%null%</text>
<text id="107003">%null%</text>
<text id="107004">%null%</text>
<text id="107005">%null%</text>
<text id="107006">%null%</text>
<text id="107007">%null%</text>
<text id="107008">%null%</text>
<text id="107009">%null%</text>
<text id="107010">This is a memory of the new flock. Of a meeting between the Guardian and a witch, both of whom were guided to the Roundtable Hold.

"There. Though I doubt thou wilt soar the skies as once thou didst..."

So murmured the Recluse, gently stroking the wing in sympathy. The Guardian felt the curse that eats away at his wing recede, its progress halted. He thanked her with courtesy, but the Recluse just shook her head in silence.

"'Tis nothing. 'Twas for such times I learned what I did..."

The Guardian turned his eye to a nearby pile of books. "Perhaps, if armed with knowledge, I might have saved them," he thought. It was from thence that the Guardian began to address the Recluse as his teacher.</text>
<text id="107011">%null%</text>
<text id="107012">%null%</text>
<text id="107013">%null%</text>
<text id="107014">%null%</text>
<text id="107015">%null%</text>
<text id="107016">%null%</text>
<text id="107017">%null%</text>
<text id="107018">%null%</text>
<text id="107019">%null%</text>
<text id="107020">This is a memory of the old flock. 

In formation they took to the skies, cutting through the air with the ease of a single living being. From his vantage amongst the clouds, the Guardian spied the citadel below.

A hail of spears came hurtling from the ramparts. This was all part of their duty, as winged warriors of the scapular regiment.

The Guardian's corps took the van to shield the greater flock from the incoming projectiles, before receding to allow the talon regiment to plunge into the fortress. It would not stand for long.

In was through battle that the flock was whole. Until the cursed blades would come to rob them of their wings.</text>
<text id="107021">%null%</text>
<text id="107022">%null%</text>
<text id="107023">%null%</text>
<text id="107024">%null%</text>
<text id="107025">%null%</text>
<text id="107026">%null%</text>
<text id="107027">%null%</text>
<text id="107028">%null%</text>
<text id="107029">%null%</text>
<text id="107030">This is a memory of the new flock. Of a lesson learned at the Roundtable Hold.

"Bwahaha! Just put it on, I fixed it up for you, friend!"

The man known as the Raider was bold and boisterous.

"I knew it would be perfect for a fine knight of your stature!"

He was also a terrible meddler, and willful in his way. Having had the helm foisted upon him, the Guardian instinctively batted it away.

He knew the Raider had meant no harm, but he had simply laid down his helm long ago. Ever since the day he lost the flock he failed to protect.</text>
<text id="107031">%null%</text>
<text id="107032">%null%</text>
<text id="107033">%null%</text>
<text id="107034">%null%</text>
<text id="107035">%null%</text>
<text id="107036">%null%</text>
<text id="107037">%null%</text>
<text id="107038">%null%</text>
<text id="107039">%null%</text>
<text id="107040">This is a memory of the old flock.

The Guardian was the sole survivor of a war in which there was no hope of victory.

It was in battle that the flock was whole, and could rebuff any and all who dared face them.

Knights of the Pinionfolk feared not death. It was their duty and their pride to give themselves for the sake of the whole. The flock would always grow new feathers.

But with ease it was that the cursed blades stole from the flock their wholeness and unity, by instilling in them the fear of losing their flight.

Before the curse, the Guardian's shield was powerless.</text>
<text id="107041">%null%</text>
<text id="107042">%null%</text>
<text id="107043">%null%</text>
<text id="107044">%null%</text>
<text id="107045">%null%</text>
<text id="107046">%null%</text>
<text id="107047">%null%</text>
<text id="107048">%null%</text>
<text id="107049">%null%</text>
<text id="107050">This is a memory of the new flock.

While in the study, in wafted the alluring savor of freshly-baked bread. The taciturn warrior must have been in a mind to cook.

Led by the aroma in the courtyard, the pirate's bellowing laughter rang out. The archer had an arrow aimed at the big man. The Guardian had no mind to stop their amusement, for he knew they were merely making merry. The swordsman said not a word, and headed to his easel.

They were a flock that was far from whole, imbalanced and uneven. He wondered if the word even truly applied.

It was around that time that the unfamiliar merchant arrived.</text>
<text id="107051">%null%</text>
<text id="107052">%null%</text>
<text id="107053">%null%</text>
<text id="107054">%null%</text>
<text id="107055">%null%</text>
<text id="107056">%null%</text>
<text id="107057">%null%</text>
<text id="107058">%null%</text>
<text id="107059">%null%</text>
<text id="107060">This is a memory of the new flock.

After taking care of the Merchant, the Guardian heard a voice coming from behind.

"I suppose thou wert protecting thy flock?" said the Recluse.

"Indeed, Mistress. I consider our fellows of the Roundtable to be as you say."

In response the Recluse nodded her head, unspeaking for a moment, then "I know the laws of thy people. Thou wilt not suffer those who endanger the flock to remain."

There was within the merchant's ledger a clue pertaining to the cursed blades. He asked the Iron Menial to help investigate.</text>
<text id="107061">%null%</text>
<text id="107062">%null%</text>
<text id="107063">%null%</text>
<text id="107064">%null%</text>
<text id="107065">%null%</text>
<text id="107066">%null%</text>
<text id="107067">%null%</text>
<text id="107068">%null%</text>
<text id="107069">%null%</text>
<text id="107070">This is a memory of the new flock.

The third volume collected laid bare the secrets of the cursed weapon known as the Ictarus.

"The curse is the product of a sorcery from deep within distant land. A script put down in blood."

The Guardian remembered reading about this particular variety of magic. "Knowledge and knowing lead to protection." So he believed, of his knowledge gained under the tutelage of his teacher.

The Guardian knew now, for certain. He knew now of many stories: The tale of the pack of horses galloping across Windwail Knoll, the great adventures of the pirates of the coastal waters, the fearsome "Fellowship," the wandering warrior whose habit was to preserve scenes with brush and ink. And finally, the tale of the witch of the deep woods, who wielded cursed magics...</text>
<text id="107071">%null%</text>
<text id="107072">%null%</text>
<text id="107073">%null%</text>
<text id="107074">%null%</text>
<text id="107075">%null%</text>
<text id="107076">%null%</text>
<text id="107077">%null%</text>
<text id="107078">%null%</text>
<text id="107079">%null%</text>
<text id="107080">This is a memory of the new flock.

The Guardian was forced to make a decision for the safety of the flock.

Eyes closed as he contemplated matters, someone approached.

"I do not like to interfere."

Across from him stood a girl who seemed more doll than human. The newest feather to find home within the flock. 

"However, I owe the witch a debt. Even with what you now know, it is not too late."

And with that she left, leaving behind a scrap of paper.</text>
<text id="107081">%null%</text>
<text id="107082">%null%</text>
<text id="107083">%null%</text>
<text id="107084">%null%</text>
<text id="107085">%null%</text>
<text id="107086">%null%</text>
<text id="107087">%null%</text>
<text id="107088">%null%</text>
<text id="107089">%null%</text>
<text id="107090">This is a memory of the new flock.

The Guardian could not bring himself to harm the Recluse.

Though she was indeed the one who birthed the curse which wrenched away the wings of his former flock, she was one feather utterly essential to the new. The Guardian weighed both thoughts in his mind.

He knew then what it was that he must protect. And as proof of his knighthood, his very resolution, he would don the helm that the giant of a man had mended for his wear. Taking it in hand, the Guardian stepped forth with renewed purpose.</text>
<text id="108000">Trying to escape from the encroachment of the Night, I awoke.

Checking my joints, I traced my way through clouded memories.

...But where was I? And why did the air smell of must and mold?

I needed to know what was going on. That is where I decided to begin.</text>
<text id="108001">%null%</text>
<text id="108002">%null%</text>
<text id="108003">%null%</text>
<text id="108004">%null%</text>
<text id="108005">%null%</text>
<text id="108006">%null%</text>
<text id="108007">%null%</text>
<text id="108008">%null%</text>
<text id="108009">%null%</text>
<text id="108010">As I have fought alongside the others of the Roundtable Hold, some of the fog surrounding my memories has lifted.

I look in the mirror.

I remember my name is Daphne. Daughter of the prestigious House of Northerncroft, a family of master puppeteers.

But, then, upon the day of a fearsome storm, the Night swallowed the entirety of the family estate. It was on that day that I became the Revenant, taking on the figure of this doll.</text>
<text id="108011">%null%</text>
<text id="108012">%null%</text>
<text id="108013">%null%</text>
<text id="108014">%null%</text>
<text id="108015">%null%</text>
<text id="108016">%null%</text>
<text id="108017">%null%</text>
<text id="108018">%null%</text>
<text id="108019">%null%</text>
<text id="108020">Though my form is that of a doll, yet do I dream.

Upon the night of the storm, nothing stirs within the estate, except for me, now inhabiting the unfamiliar body of a doll, aimlessly prowling the grounds. Then, something strokes my cheek.

It is ever at this point that the dream is cut short. I awaken and look in the mirror—so I can make sure of the sensations running through me. 

"Are my dreams not enough, that you desire more?"

Black streaks have appeared upon my cheeks. It seems I am cherished by the Night indeed, to think it would still give chase, even in this doll's frame.</text>
<text id="108021">%null%</text>
<text id="108022">%null%</text>
<text id="108023">%null%</text>
<text id="108024">%null%</text>
<text id="108025">%null%</text>
<text id="108026">%null%</text>
<text id="108027">%null%</text>
<text id="108028">%null%</text>
<text id="108029">%null%</text>
<text id="108030">In the mirror, I conceal the ways in which the Night eats away at me. As I apply the cosmetics given to me by the Iron Menial, I recall his words to me.

"Within your memories is a hole of not inconsequential size. It seems that the Night is using this toehold to take root."

The Recluse was the one who made this observation, but I know not how much she is worth my trust.

That aside, I cannot grow accustomed to applying makeup with my own hand. Back at home, someone would have done it for me.

The task finally complete, I caress the smoothness of my cheeks. Now I come to think of it, what was the name I gave this doll?</text>
<text id="108031">%null%</text>
<text id="108032">%null%</text>
<text id="108033">%null%</text>
<text id="108034">%null%</text>
<text id="108035">%null%</text>
<text id="108036">%null%</text>
<text id="108037">%null%</text>
<text id="108038">%null%</text>
<text id="108039">%null%</text>
<text id="108040">I look into the mirror. The Night eats away at more and more.

"Pitiful..."

She was my darling baby, carved by my Grandfather. I called her by a name, but I don't know if I'll ever recall it now. Instead I stroke her face.

I must find a way to purge my body of the Night that is nesting within. In that case, I believe the Priestess...</text>
<text id="108041">The Revenant succumbed to sleep.
Regaining consciousness, she found herself in a familiar building. A place she could never forget; the mansion, on the very night of the storm. Up stood the Revenant.

Entering the room at the end of the corridor, the shapes of people appeared one after another. They attacked, almost as if trying to cling to her, but in the end the stagnation was driven away.

Opening her eyes, she was greeted by the witch's face. The discoloration had gone, her body was her own to control again.

The Revenant said that the situation was resolved, but she made no mention of the ill feeling that remained in the pit of her stomach.</text>
<text id="108042">%null%</text>
<text id="108043">%null%</text>
<text id="108044">%null%</text>
<text id="108045">%null%</text>
<text id="108046">%null%</text>
<text id="108047">%null%</text>
<text id="108048">%null%</text>
<text id="108049">%null%</text>
<text id="108050">Dolls too have their dreams. This I know.

The daughter of the house softly caresses my cheeks.

"Let's put on a little makeup, Daphne."

I always liked having my makeup done.</text>
<text id="108051">%null%</text>
<text id="108052">%null%</text>
<text id="108053">%null%</text>
<text id="108054">%null%</text>
<text id="108055">%null%</text>
<text id="108056">%null%</text>
<text id="108057">%null%</text>
<text id="108058">%null%</text>
<text id="108059">%null%</text>
<text id="108060">I caress the cheeks of the face that looks back from the mirror.

These fingers have not the warmth, nor the softness I expect.

It seems I must face again what transpired upon that stormy night.</text>
<text id="108061">%null%</text>
<text id="108062">%null%</text>
<text id="108063">%null%</text>
<text id="108064">%null%</text>
<text id="108065">%null%</text>
<text id="108066">%null%</text>
<text id="108067">%null%</text>
<text id="108068">%null%</text>
<text id="108069">%null%</text>
<text id="108070">I grasp the portrait and face the mirror.

The daughter of the house is no more. She will never caress my face again, no matter how I yearn.

I never was a human. And now, the mantle of doll no longer fits me.

There is but one thing that I must accomplish—the every reason I became the Revenant. To bring an end to the night of the storm.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>