<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
  <compression>None</compression>
  <version>DarkSouls3</version>
  <bigendian>False</bigendian>
  <entries>
    <text id="252910">The effects of the Scholar's Analyse skill change depending on skill progress (low, mid, or max) and targets.

When targeting enemies:
Low: Reduce enemy attack power
Mid: Further reduce enemy attack
Max: One-time bonus damage to target

When targeting self:
Low: Raise max stamina
Mid: Further raise max stamina
Max: Temporary one-time damage negation
         + launch wave when hit

When activated on self, the highest progress level within range is applied.

Skill progress is affected by the status of enemies and allies, by observations of certain actions, and types of collected specimens.

N.B. Analyse mode camera speed can be changed in system menu.</text>
    <text id="302100">The Scholar has joined the warriors of the Roundtable.

Choose him to depart on expeditions like any other player character.

The Scholar is a support character who gains advantages by manipulating the battlefield, analysing enemies and threading them together.</text>
    <text id="302101">%null%</text>
    <text id="302102">%null%</text>
    <text id="302103">%null%</text>
    <text id="302104">%null%</text>
    <text id="302105">%null%</text>
    <text id="302106">%null%</text>
    <text id="302107">%null%</text>
    <text id="302108">%null%</text>
    <text id="302109">%null%</text>
    <text id="302110">The Undertaker has joined the warriors of the Roundtable.

Choose her to depart on expeditions like any other player character.

The Undertaker is an offensive character who can execute persistent attacks by fluently evading enemy onslaughts.</text>
    <text id="403147">Likely spots for armaments and items at key locations are indicated by the following icons on the detailed view of the map.

&lt;?image@4166##6?&gt;: Skill-changing smithing table

&lt;?keyicon@308?&gt; on Map menu: Detailed view</text>
    <text id="403240">鍛冶師たちの集落です。炉に火を加えるとスキルを変更できます。</text>
    <text id="403241">%null%</text>
    <text id="403242">%null%</text>
    <text id="403243">%null%</text>
    <text id="403244">%null%</text>
    <text id="403245">%null%</text>
    <text id="403246">%null%</text>
    <text id="403247">%null%</text>
    <text id="403248">%null%</text>
    <text id="403249">%null%</text>
    <text id="403250">Key locations are indicated by the following icons:

&lt;?image@4185##6?&gt;: Resonating Crystal
Crystals found in the Great Hollow, part of the root system of the giant crystals. Their resonance is said to cause giant crystals to shatter.

&lt;?image@4183##6?&gt;: Eastern Underground Fort
A fortress seeped in deepest Night, enshrouded by crystal curse.

&lt;?image@4184##6?&gt;: Western Underground Fort
A fortress in which clandestine research was conducted, enshrouded by crystal curse.

&lt;?image@4182##6?&gt;: Temple
A magnificent and sacred structure, in which remembrances of battle slumber. Rainbow-colored Order is bestowed upon all who take up its challenge.</text>
    <text id="403440">A great cavity in the depths of Limveld. A sacred tower can be seen from the waterfall and the hollow is strewn with giant crystals, but much of it is decrepit and the ground is cracking open.

The area is peppered with exotic ruins, the only things that remain of an ancient people, and a temple is buttressed by two forts, one each to the east and west, where the cursed miasma that exudes from the crystals eats away at life.

Neutralizing the curse requires the protective blessing of a great crystal.</text>
    <text id="403460">On the Change Skill menu, it is possible to replace the skill attached to a weapon in your possession.

The new weapon skill is determined at random and a skill can only be replaced once per smithing table.

After changing the weapon skill, the smithing table can be used a single time to revert to the original skill.

Multiple players can change skills at the same smithing table.</text>
    <text id="403461">%null%</text>
    <text id="403462">%null%</text>
    <text id="403463">%null%</text>
    <text id="403464">%null%</text>
    <text id="403465">%null%</text>
    <text id="403466">%null%</text>
    <text id="403467">%null%</text>
    <text id="403468">%null%</text>
    <text id="403469">%null%</text>
    <text id="403470">Dormant Power grants hidden potential and can be obtained by defeating bosses at key locations.

Choose a reward from the offerings. If it is an item, it can be left behind.

Each item is chosen by multiple players.

&lt;?keyicon@204?&gt;: Choose power to obtain
&lt;?keyicon@209?&gt;: Leave item behind</text>
  </entries>
</fmg>